KEVIN LI



klix18design@gmail.com

New York

Professional Summary

Automation Specialist with proven success designing, building, and scaling enterprise Airtable systems and workflows. At NBCUniversal, created automated pipelines that increased efficiency by 500%, saved over \$2M in projected engineering costs, and enabled single-operator management of high-volume content workflows.

Education

Pratt Institute

BFA Graphic Design Major UI/UX Design Minor Graduated with Highest Honors

Victoria Education

Generative AI Applications

Skills

Airtable; Python, Shell scripts; Prompt Engineering, RAG, Fine-tuning; Figma; Miro; Illustrator, Photoshop; HTML, CSS, jQuery; Webflow; Spline; Blender; DAM, CMS

Languages

English (Native)
Mandarin (Native)

Experiences

NBC Universal

Automation Designer

08/2024 - present, New York

- Designed and built an entire end-to-end automated workflow using Airtable, Photoshop scripts, and shell commands, enabling asynchronous cross-team collaboration and delivering 20,000+ images in 30 days.
- Automated enterprise-scale Airtable data structures and workflows supporting imagery, saving over 2 million dollars for the company.
- Developed automated workflows with custom Photoshop scripts, shell commands, python scripts, and Airtable automation.
- Trained and supported 18+ team members through workshops, documentation, and ongoing troubleshooting.
- Designed and built an automated system that reduces work time from 1 hour to 10 minutes, boosting efficiency by 500% while enhancing accuracy by minimizing human error.
- Created step-by-step, onboarding user guidelines.
- Streamlined the DAM and CMS systems for SkyShowTime to be efficient and simple to use.

Freelance

UX Designer

06/2024 - present, New York

- Lead the end-to-end design and build of Sizemore Insurance's new website, which yielded a 200% increase in leads rate, from 5% to 15%.
- Responsible for creating Sizemore Insurance's visual identity.
- Art directed and designed meta adverstisments for Sizemore Insurance in motion and still.

Warner Brothers Discovery

Contract Graphic Designer

06/2024 - present, Remote

- Art directing and creating pitch decks, album art, and end credits while handling multiple, time-sensitive requests at once.

Graphic Design Intern

06/2023 - 12/2023, Los Angeles

 Developed a broad range of design materials, including website interfaces, motion graphics, posters, signage, wayfinding, emails pitch-decks, and various show collaterals in digital and print.

Agentize.ai

Al Design Intern

03/2024 - 06/2024, Toronto

- Prompt-engineered, RAG, and fine tuned GenAl models. Crafted interactive user interfaces for hardware and software.